# **Alexander Replyansky**

# **Full Stack Developer**

054-877-3839 | alexander-replyansky@yandex.ru Github | LinkedIn

#### **SUMMARY**

Full Stack Developer experienced in Python and JavaScript based programming with a background in web application development. Possess strong skills in Python frameworks and database management systems. Highly skilled in programming design, development, and implementation of functional specifications..

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Python, OOP, SQL, Flask, Django, Javascript, HTML5, CSS3, Git.

#### **TECHNICAL PROJECTS**

## Browser game - Github | Demo

Webpage game with interactive elements and different scenarios.

- Styled the game, organizing style in style.css file.
- Implemented the animation and moving objects using Javascript setInterval method.
- Built in sound effects and background music by employing HTML5 audio elements with certain settings adjusted in attributes.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Service Representative**

Tel Aviv District, Israel

**Bynet Semech** 

2023 - present

Bynet Semech provides a comprehensive range of end-to-end solutions and professional services that meet the rapidly evolving IT and telecom needs of companies in Israel.

- Consulting in the department of Authority for the Rights of Holocaust Survivors
- Managing databases via CRM
- Assisting with specific issues related to the rights of Holocaust survivors

## Receptionist / Administrator

Saint Petersburg, Russia

Jewish Charity Center

2020 - 2022

- Provided information for clients on telephone line
- Edited timetables and worked with documents via MS Office
- Contacted with contractors and made purchases if it was needed

**Checkpoint guard** Atlit, Israel IDF Service 2014 - 2016

- Checked the entry cards for those wishing to enter the territory of the base
- Carried weapon and was responsible for its safeness and serviceability
- Patrolled the area of checkpoint and surveyed the surrounding area

# **EDUCATION**

## Full Stack Web Development, Python and JavaScript program

Developers Institute, TLV Coding Bootcamp

Ramat Gan, Israel 01/2023 - 05/2023

#### **Liberal Arts and Sciences**

Saint Petersburg State University

Saint Petersburg, Russia

### **LANGUAGES**

**English** - full professional proficiency

**Hebrew** - professional working proficiency

Russian - native

2017-2019